Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5149
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ICC FD 22425, 22428 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- ICC FD 22429, 22432, 22437 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- ICC FD 22240, 22408, 22252, 22453 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- ICC FD 22337 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- ICC FD 22331, 22341-22345, 22356 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- ICC FD 22363, 22365, 22366 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- ICC FD 22200-22295 (A) (Box 9, Folder 12)
- ICC FD 22200-22295 (B) (Box 9, Folder 13)
- ICC FD 22200-22295 (C) (Box 9, Folder 14)
- ICC FD 22200-22295 (D) (Box 9, Folder 15)
- ICC FD 21900-21991 (A) (Box 9, Folder 16)
- ICC FD 21900-21991 (B) (Box 9, Folder 17)
- ICC FD 21900-21991 (C) (Box 9, Folder 18)
- ICC FD 21900-21991 (D) (Box 9, Folder 19)
- ICC FD 22300-22399 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- ICC FD 22700-22799, Pt. 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- ICC FD 22700-22799, Pt. 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- ICC FD 22700-22799, Pt. 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- ICC FD 22700-22799, Pt. 4 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- ICC FD 22600-22696, Pt. 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- ICC FD 22600-22696, Pt. 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- ICC FD 22600-22696, Pt. 3 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- ICC FD 23204-23295, Pt. 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- ICC FD 23204-23295, Pt. 2 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- ICC FD 23204-23295, Pt. 3 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- ICC FD 22902-22995, Pt. 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- ICC FD 22902-22995, Pt. 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- ICC FD 22902-22995, Pt. 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- ICC FD 22902-22995, Pt. 4 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- ICC FD 23000-23099, Pt. 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- ICC FD 23000-23099, Pt. 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- ICC FD 22802-22896, Pt. 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- ICC FD 22802-22896, Pt. 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- ICC FD 22802-22896, Pt. 3 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- ICC FD 22802-22896, Pt. 4 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- ICC FD 22802-22896, Pt. 5 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- ICC FD 23305-23395, Pt. 1 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- ICC FD 23305-23395, Pt. 2 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- ICC FD 23305-23395, Pt. 3 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- ICC FD 23401-23500, Pt. 1 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- ICC FD 23401-23500, Pt. 2 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- ICC FD 23401-23500, Pt. 3 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- ICC FD 23401-23500, Pt. 4 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- ICC FD 23401-23500, Pt. 5 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- ICC FD 23100-23195, Pt. 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- ICC FD 23100-23195, Pt. 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- ICC FD 23100-23195, Pt. 3 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- ICC FD 23100-23195, Pt. 4 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- ICC FD 23100-23195, Pt. 5 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- ICC FD 23600-23698, Pt. 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- ICC FD 23600-23698, Pt. 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- ICC FD 23600-23698, Pt. 3 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- ICC FD 23500-23595, Pt. 1 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- ICC FD 23500-23595, Pt. 2 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- ICC FD 23500-23595, Pt. 3 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- ICC FD 23500-23595, Pt. 4 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- ICC FD 23500-23595, Pt. 5 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Special Expense Fund for the State Legislative Representatives (Box 12, Folder 14)
- ICC FD 23700-23795, Pt. 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- ICC FD 23700-23795, Pt. 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- ICC FD 23700-23795, Pt. 3 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- ICC FD 23700-23795, Pt. 4 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- ICC FD 23700-23795, Pt. 5 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- ICC FD 23700-23795, Pt. 6 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- ICC FD 23700-23795, Pt. 7 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- ICC FD 23700-23795, Pt. 8 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- ICC FD 23700-23795, Pt. 9 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- ICC FD 23700-23795, Pt. 10 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- ICC FD 23900-23999, Pt. 1 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- ICC FD 23900-23999, Pt. 2 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- ICC FD 23900-23999, Pt. 3 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- ICC FD 23900-23999, Pt. 4 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- ICC FD 23900-23999, Pt. 5 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- ICC FD 24000-24098, Pt. 1 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- ICC FD 24000-24098, Pt. 2 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- ICC FD 2400-24098, Pt. 3 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- ICC FD 24000-24098, Pt. 4 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- ICC FD 24000-24098, Pt. 5 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- BRT Files (Box 14, Folder 1)
- ICC FD 24000-24986, Pt. 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- ICC FD 24000-24986, Pt. 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- ICC FD 24000-24986, Pt. 3 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- ICC FD 24000-24986, Pt. 4 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- ICC FD 24000-24986, Pt. 5 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- ICC FD 23800-23885, Pt. 1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- ICC FD 23800-23885, Pt. 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- ICC FD 23800-23885, Pt. 3 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- ICC FD 23800-23885, Pt. 4 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- ICC FD 23800-23885, Pt. 5 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- ICC FD 23178 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- UTU Committees (Box 14, Folder 13)
- National Legislative Bds.: Related Material (Box 14, Folder 14)
- National Legislative Boards: General Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 15)
- 4300-Alaska (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- 4300-NL California (Political) 1959/60 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- 4300-California (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- 4300-Colorado (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- 4300-Florida (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- 4300-Illinois (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- 4300-Iowa (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- 4300-Kansas (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- 4300-Kentucky (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- 4300-Louisiana (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- 4300-Maine (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- 4300-Massachusetts (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- 4300-Michigan (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- 4300-Minnesota (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- 4300-Nebraska (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- 4300-New Hampshire (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- 4300-New Mexico (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- 4300-New Jersey (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- 4300-New York (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- 4300-Ohio (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- 4300-Oklahoma (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- 4300-Rhode Island (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- 4300-Pennsylvania (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- 4300-Tennessee (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- 4300-Texas (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- 4300-Utah (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- 4300-Virginia (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- 4300-Washington (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- 4300-West Virginia (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- 4300-Wisconsin (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- 4300-Wyoming (Political) 1965/66 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Correspondence Concerning Seaboard Airlines RR (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Penn RR/Penn Central RR (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Southern Railway System (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Soo Line RR Co.-Discontinuance of Service in Minnesota (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Pacific Electric Lines- General Chairman (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Railway Labor Act: Bus and Truck (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Railway Labor Act: Carriers and the RLA of 1926 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Railway Labor Act: Copies of Act. Public 257, 69th Congress (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Railroads- BRT Agreements (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Railway Labor Act: 1934, Pt. 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Railway Labor Act Amendments: April 10, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- (Status) Electric Railways Under Railway Labor Act (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Railway Act 1937-1943 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Proposed Amendment to the Railway Labor Act Re: SJ Res. 91- Report No. 1073 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Wage Controversy- Non-Operating Groups 1943-44
- RLA Amendments- 1934 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Re: Newly Enacted Amendments to the Railway Labor Act of 07/02/34 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Questionnaire: Continued Violations of the RLA (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Railway Labor Act, 1934, Pt. 2 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- State Railroad Laws, Re: flagging Material Rule #99 Survey of Rules in Effect from General Chairman and State Representative (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Rule #99, Pt. 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Rule #99, Pt. 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Rule #99, Pt. 4 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  State Legislative Board Info
- Rule 99, Pt. 5 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Superior Court of Pennsylvania (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Memo (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Compilation
- Railroad Crossings (Box 16, Folder 8)
- State Laws Requiring Motor Vehicles to Stop at Grade Crossings (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Sample Flagging Legislation to State Representatives (Box 16, Folder 10)
- S.J. Resolution 91 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Booklet- Procedural Requirements Under Railway Labor Act (Box 16, Folder 12)
- RLA List of Carriers (Box 16, Folder 13)
- RLA Amendments- 1934 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Railway Labor Act Amendments- June 21, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- RLA, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Safety: Bridges, Tracks, Trestles (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Safety Bulletins (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Safety Matters (Box 16, Folder 19)
- TPEL Canada: Right to Work Laws (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Possibility of Organization (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Congressional Record (Box 17, Folder 3)
- General Political Activity (Box 17, Folder 4)
- TPEL Ladies' Auxiliary Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 5)
- TPEL Ladies' Auxiliary c.1965-66 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Membership: National Totals, Etc. (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Membership & Contributions (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Personal Correspondence to National Chairman Luna (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Political Endorsements for Primary Election (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Political Endorsements for General Elections (1964) (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Political Endorsements for General Elections, Pt. 1 (1965-66) (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Political Endorsements for General Elections, Pt. 2 (1965-66) (Box 17, Folder 13)
- TPEL Promotions (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Reorganization 1963/Coordination 1965 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Requests c. 1966 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Requests Approved- State Funds c.1965 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Reports to the US Gov't c.1965-66 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Voting Records- US Senate/House of Representatives (Box 17, Folder 19)
- SCR: Alabama (Box 17, Folder 20)
- SCR: Alaska (Box 17, Folder 21)
- SCR: Arkansas (Box 17, Folder 22)
- SCR: Arizona (Box 17, Folder 23)
- SCR: Colorado (Box 17, Folder 24)
- SCR: Connecticut (Box 17, Folder 25)
- SCR: Delaware (Box 17, Folder 26)
- SCR: Florida (Box 17, Folder 27)
- SCR: Georgia (Box 17, Folder 28)
- SCR: Idaho (Box 17, Folder 29)
- SCR: Illinois (Box 17, Folder 30)
- SCR: Indiana (Box 17, Folder 31)
- SCR: Iowa (Box 17, Folder 32)
- SCR: Kansas (Box 17, Folder 33)
- SCR: Kentucky (Box 17, Folder 34)
- SCR: Louisiana (Box 17, Folder 35)
- SCR: Maine (Box 18, Folder 1)
- SCR: Maryland (Box 18, Folder 2)
- SCR: Massachusetts (Box 18, Folder 3)
- SCR: Michigan (Box 18, Folder 4)
- SCR: Minnesota (Box 18, Folder 5)
- SCR: Minnesota (Box 18, Folder 6)
- SCR: Mississippi (Box 18, Folder 7)
- SCR: Missouri (Box 18, Folder 8)
- SCR: Montana (Box 18, Folder 9)
- SCR: Nevada (Box 18, Folder 10)
- SCR: New Hampshire (Box 18, Folder 11)
- SCR: New Jersey (Box 18, Folder 12)
- SCR: New Mexico (Box 18, Folder 13)
- SCR: New York (Box 18, Folder 14)
- SCR: North Carolina (Box 18, Folder 15)
- SCR: North Dakota (Box 18, Folder 16)
- SCR: Ohio (Box 18, Folder 17)
- SCR: Oklahoma (Box 18, Folder 18)
- SCR: Oregon (Box 18, Folder 19)
- SCR: Pennsylvania (Box 18, Folder 20)
- SCR: Rhode Island (Box 18, Folder 21)
- SCR: South Carolina (Box 18, Folder 22)
- SCR: South Dakota (Box 18, Folder 23)
- SCR: Tennessee (Box 18, Folder 24)
- SCR: Texas (Box 18, Folder 25)
- SCR: Utah (Box 18, Folder 26)
- SCR: Vermont (Box 18, Folder 27)
- SCR: Virginia (Box 18, Folder 28)
- SCR: Washington (Box 18, Folder 29)
- SCR: West Virginia (Box 18, Folder 30)
- SCR: Wisconsin (Box 18, Folder 31)
- SCR: Wyoming (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Protest-Vacation Assignment-1961 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Vacation Agreement (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Vacation Allowances (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Vacation Allowances (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Vacations with Pay Eng. & Trainmen (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Vacation- Claims (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Agreement: Northern Pacific & BRT (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Air Hose Agreement (Box 19, Folder 2)
- BRT Rule GN Schedule (Box 19, Folder 3)
- BRT/ORE 40-Hour Week Strike, Aug. 1950 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Change-Pay Days (Box 19, Folder 5)
- GW Parker Case (Box 19, Folder 6)
- IHB Pay Agreement (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Meeting Minutes- Maine/Boston Railroad (Box 19, Folder 8)
- New Working Agreement (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Passes, Requirements, and Registration Forms (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Power Brake, Law of (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Resignations (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Rule on Crews Passing Limit Board (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Toledo- Div. Advertising for Percentage (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Transfers: To and From Train Service (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Union Shop (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Wage Increases (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Wage Rates: BRT, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Wage Rules: 1943 Strike (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Wage Rules: 1950 Strike (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Wage Rules: Application of Yard Article 24 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Wage Rules: Chicago, W. Pullman & S.R.R. (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Wage Rules: Correspondence With Train Master- Toledo-Div. D.E. Faris (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Wage Rules: Delaware, Lackawanna, Western RR (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Wage Rules: Dispute- BLE; BLF&E ORC (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Wage Rules: Extra Board Montezuma- Morefield (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Wage Rules: Fourth Man on Yard Crew (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Wage Rules: General Yardmaster- Correspondence, W.D. Daniels (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Wage Rules: Local Agreements (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Wage Rules: Operation of RR Army (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Wage Rules: Oregon-Washington RR (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Wage Rules: Other Brotherhoods (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Wage Rules: Rule 14 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- Wage Rules: Seniority Rules (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Wage Rules: Southern Pacific RR (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Wage Rules: Trainmaster Correspondence- E.C. Morgan (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Wage Rules: Wellston Yard Agreement (Box 19, Folder 37)
- Wage Rules: Yard-Crew Work Without Full Crew (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Wage Rules: Yard Helpers- Qualifying [sic] as Foremen (Box 19, Folder 39)
- Wage Rules: Yard Helpers- Rate of Pay Switch Tenders (B&O System) (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Wage Rules: Yardmaster Rulings (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Watch Inspection Regulations (Box 19, Folder 42)
- Work Train & Construction Service (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Yard Assignments & Filling Vacancies (Box 19, Folder 44)
- Yard Decisions (Box 19, Folder 45)
- Yard Rate of Pay (Box 19, Folder 46)
- Yards, Springfield B&C and Alton (Box 19, Folder 47)
- Bulletins (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Cases Closed by Sub-General Committee Action- Baltimore (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Cases Closed in Sub-Committee Meeting-Cleveland (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Claims Adjusted (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Claims- Terminal Air Test (Box 20, Folder 5)
- E.J. Ashen- Case (Box 20, Folder 6)
- General Grievance Committees, Pt. 1 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- General Grievance Committees, Pt. 2 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- General Grievance Committees, Pt. 3 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Geo. Seaborg. (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Interest of 6% on All Claims Not Settled by Railroads Within 90 Days (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Joe Wood- Claim (Box 20, Folder 12)
- L.C. Woody Dismissed Cases (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Lodge 1000: Yard Extra Lest-MFLD (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Men hours Worked-Springfield, Ill. (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Mileage-Tuscola-Air Claims (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Pilot Services (Box 20, Folder 17)
- R.M. Pygman Reinstatement Case (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Relinquishing Conductor Rights (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Report of Standing Committee (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Resignations, Rejection Service Application (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Road Bulletins- Indianapolis Division (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Seniority Claims Employees Discharged (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Service Men Presuming Duties on Toledo Division (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Subcommittee Cases, Pt. 1 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Subcommittee Cases, Pt. 2 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Sub-Committee Meeting Cintio 6-23-61 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Terminal Rule (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Time Limit on Claims (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Toledo O. Furloughed & Man Called Back (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Toledo O. Resignations & DSRP Men (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Work Claim Decision (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Work Claims/Grievances, Misc. Pt. 1 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Work Claims/Grievances, Misc. Pt. 2 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Work Claims/Grievances, Misc. Pt. 3 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Work Claims/Grievances, Misc. Pt. 4 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Yard Bulletins (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Yard Men Used in Road Service (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Yard Rulings, General (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Wage Rules: Lodge (LS) Coffin #311, Part 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Wage Rules: Lodge (LS) Coffin #311, Part 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Wage Rules: Lodge (LS) Coffin #311, Part 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- PSF Work Claims: Pittsburgh & Lake Erie, Part 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- PSF Work Claims: Pittsburgh & Lake Erie, Part 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- PSF Work Claims: Pittsburgh & Lake Erie, Part 3 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- PSF Work Claims: Pittsburgh & Lake Erie, Part 4 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Work Claims/Grievances (Box 21, Folder 8)
  A series of files, unfoldered for now
- Lodge #1, Part 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Lodge #1, Part 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Lodge Notebook #1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Lodge Notebook #2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Lodge Notebook #3 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Meeting Minutes (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Record Book, 1906-1912 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Record Book, 1912-1919 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Record Book, 1919-1923 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Record Book, 1924-1929 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Record Book, 1929-1936 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Record Book, 1936-1942 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Record Book, 1943-1947 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Record Book, 1948-1953 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Record Book, 1953-1959 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Record Book, 1959-1965 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Policy Register: Perseverance Lodge #96, A-N (Box 23, Folder 11)
  Membership List for Ladies' Auxiliary of the BRT in Oneonta, NY
- Policy Register: Perseverance Lodge #96, O to W (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Policy Register: Membership Names A Thru J (Box 23, Folder 13)
  Recopied July 1967. Obsolete.
- Policy Register: Perseverance Lodge #96, K to Z (Box 23, Folder 14)
  Recopied 1967. Obsolete.
- Policy Register: Perseverance Lodge, A-M (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Policy Register: Perseverance Lodge #96, M-W (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Minutes, 1885-1890 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Minutes 1892-1897 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1907-1918 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Lodge book, 1909-1913 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Minutes, 1936-1947 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1947-1959 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- V.E. Hall (Box 25, Folder 1)
- L. H. Haan (Box 25, Folder 2)
- J. Chapman (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Time Claim Bro. C.F. van Epps (Box 25, Folder 4)
- L. Schepp (Box 25, Folder 5)
- H.I. Jacobs (Box 25, Folder 6)
- D. La Prease (Box 25, Folder 7)
- D.H. Hill (Box 25, Folder 8)
- R.H. Monnington (Box 25, Folder 9)
- H.C. Sutton (Box 25, Folder 10)
- A. Cowen (Box 25, Folder 11)
- P.J. Carrie (Box 25, Folder 12)
- F.G. Davison (Box 25, Folder 13)
- F. H. Canton (Box 25, Folder 14)
- P. Hobb and Crew (Box 25, Folder 15)
- R.H. Monnington (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Puller #5 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- J.H. Fritzen (Box 25, Folder 18)
- H.D. Smith (Box 25, Folder 19)
- J.A. Doyle (Box 25, Folder 20)
- J. Albanese (Box 25, Folder 21)
- V.N. Costello (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Bro. R.A. Hill (Box 25, Folder 23)
- L.A. Walrath (Box 25, Folder 24)
- M.L. Caroll (Box 25, Folder 25)
- David Casprus (Box 25, Folder 26)
- C.B. Bergan, P.R. Careny, R.R. Hammond, C.A. Dowling (Box 25, Folder 27)
- W.J. Barrett, H.P. Hutchins, and H.D. Burtch- Mechanicsville (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Time Claim- W. Kaczmaryczyk (Box 25, Folder 29)
- C.D. van Schaack (Box 25, Folder 30)
- J.B. Gallery Crew (Box 25, Folder 31)
- W.J. Barrett-Crew (Box 25, Folder 32)
- W. Silver, R. Mosher (Box 25, Folder 33)
- N. Gerthoffer (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Dispute Regrouping Ft. Assignments on Mohawk Div. and Bru Territory (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Yard Agreement Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Condr. K.R. Taubman; Bkmn J.E. Haley, E. Perry, and F. Kenyon (Box 25, Folder 37)
- J.J. Crowley (Box 25, Folder 38)
- R.E. Hotchkiss (Box 25, Folder 39)
- W.J. Barrett, K.J. Cramer, A.M. Kilts, J.P. Fogarty, M.F. Deegan (Box 25, Folder 40)
- J.F. Saroney, N. Denbleyker, R.S. Rogers (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Claim: K. Rosby (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Claim: A.L. Knapp, E. Perry, E.G. Klossner, G.A. McCarthy (Box 25, Folder 43)
- J.C. Frey and Crew (Box 25, Folder 44)
- East Bound out of DeWitt (Box 25, Folder 45)
- D.B. Chaffee Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 46)
- A.L. Raynor (Box 25, Folder 47)
- S.J. Groat, K.J. 1Gramer, H.D. Burtch, L.R. Chase (Box 25, Folder 48)
- W.C. Merritt (Box 25, Folder 49)
- R.E. Hotchkiss, P.F. Sammons (Box 25, Folder 50)
- H.E. Merriam Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 51)
- J. Tallman Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 52)
- R.A. Hesselbarth (Box 25, Folder 53)
- R.J. Nolan Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 54)
- J.F. Duane Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 55)
- R.H. Morrington (Box 25, Folder 56)
- C.R. Kasdoff (Box 25, Folder 57)
- D.E. Pudney Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 58)
- T.E. Phelps (Box 25, Folder 59)
- D.E. Costello Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 60)
- T.H. Martin Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 61)
- G.C. Costello Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 62)
- W.E. Boland Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 63)
- G.H. Little boy Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 64)
- S.F. Lee Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 65)
- T.J. Sultan Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 66)
- L.H. Haar Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 67)
- J. Albanese Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 68)
- J.F. Metrick Lot Claims (Box 25, Folder 69)
- F.J. Haley, G.H. Lawrence (Box 25, Folder 70)
- W.H. Raynor (Box 25, Folder 71)
- W. McComer (Box 25, Folder 72)
- M. Salce, L.D. Antis, E.L. Kennedy (Box 25, Folder 73)
- R. Hiltbrand (Box 25, Folder 74)
- F.C. O'Donnell Crew (Box 25, Folder 75)
- A.M. Kilts (Box 25, Folder 76)
- R.E. Hotchkiss, A. Wellisch (Box 25, Folder 77)
- R. Hiltebrand (Box 25, Folder 78)
- M.P. Bullion (Box 25, Folder 79)
- J.B. Gallery, J.E. Mosher, P.F. O'Leary, C. Butler (Box 25, Folder 80)
- R.E. Hotchkiss and Eleven Other Brakemen (Box 25, Folder 81)
- H.B. Carroll (Box 25, Folder 82)
- J.B. Gallery, Crew Perform Yard Service With Train YD-1 (Box 25, Folder 83)
- C.C. Oot and Crew (Box 25, Folder 84)
- Helper F.A. Bennick (Box 25, Folder 85)
- H.P. Hutchins and Crew (Box 25, Folder 86)
- E. Perry (Box 25, Folder 87)
- G.M. Spellman (Box 25, Folder 88)
- B.L. Cummings (Box 25, Folder 89)
- C.J. Nuffer (Box 25, Folder 90)
- D.B. Russell (Box 25, Folder 91)
- O.J. Mulholland (Box 25, Folder 92)
- A.L. McClary (Box 25, Folder 93)
- H.P. Hutchins (Box 25, Folder 94)
- D.J. Stevenson (Box 25, Folder 95)
- J.J. Welch (Box 25, Folder 96)
- T.G. Flynn (Box 25, Folder 97)
- B.H. Dickinson (Box 25, Folder 98)
- N.J. Cross (Box 25, Folder 99)
- D.A. Shoemaker, F.H. White, F.H. O'Brien (Box 25, Folder 100)
- Mishandled at DeWitt (Box 25, Folder 101)
- F.H. Barlow (Box 25, Folder 102)
- C.P. Stevenson, E.A. Richmond, E.A. Russell (Box 25, Folder 103)
- J. Albanese (Box 25, Folder 104)
- D.J. Sanderson (Box 25, Folder 105)
- J. Polochi (Box 25, Folder 106)
- J.J. DeLeo (Box 25, Folder 107)
- R. Montville, J.L. Wright, G.F. Potter, H.D. Vedder (Box 25, Folder 108)
- P.M. Steadily (Box 25, Folder 109)
- G.H. Wells, Jr. (Box 25, Folder 110)
- W.J. Barrett (Box 25, Folder 111)
- Hotchkiss, Farrar, Coughlin, Harris (Box 25, Folder 112)
- S.J. Groat (Box 25, Folder 113)
- R.L. Darrow (Box 25, Folder 114)
- G.H. Littleboy (Box 25, Folder 115)
- S.J. Groat (Box 25, Folder 116)
- G.L. Heffron (Box 25, Folder 117)
- R.J. Mosher (Box 25, Folder 118)
- J. Tallman, M. Sherbeck (Box 25, Folder 119)
- E.C. Hale, J.F. Duane, f. DeVeronica (Box 25, Folder 120)
- G.M. Spellman, E. Perry (Box 25, Folder 121)
- J.J. Welch (Box 25, Folder 122)
- T.H. Martin (Box 25, Folder 123)
- Vote of Lodges (Box 25, Folder 124)
- Water and Toilets in Towers at DeWitt (Box 25, Folder 125)
- Time Claim Grievance by G.E. Gale (Box 25, Folder 126)
- Grievance of Bro. J.F. Sherman (Box 25, Folder 127)
- Case C.W. Featherly (Box 25, Folder 128)
- P.G. Di Martino (Box 25, Folder 129)
- E.L. Burke (Box 25, Folder 130)
- R.L. Darrow (Box 25, Folder 131)
- J. Metrick (Box 25, Folder 132)
- M.M. Bolowski (Box 25, Folder 133)
- B.L. Cummings (Box 25, Folder 134)